http://www.ecusa.anglican.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets forth the privacy practices of The Episcopal Church and The Domestic and Foreign Missionary Society of the Protestant Episcopal Church in the United States of America (collectively, the “Episcopal Church”).  This policy only applies to information we collect from visitors to EpiscopalChurch.org and its family of websites (including DeputyNews.org, EpiscopalArchives.org, EpiscopalCommonPrayer.org, EpiscopalFederalChaplains.org, EpiscopalMigrationMinistries.org, EpiscopalNewsService.org, EpiscopalServiceCorps.org, GeneralConvention.org, HouseofDeputies.org, Latinosepiscopales.org, OTMportfolio.org, episcopalgbec.org, collegeforbishops.org, and titleiv.org) and explains how we treat your personal information.
The Episcopal Church collects the personal information that you make available via our website, including first and last name, email address, phone number, other contact details, news stories, survey responses, photos, payment information, and cookie data.  We also collect some information automatically about your computer hardware and software, which can include IP address, browser type, domain name, access times, and referring website addresses.  The information that we automatically collect does not by itself identify specific individuals and is statistical data typically aggregated with other data to help us improve our website.  The Episcopal Church collects your information when you provide consent; for purposes which are required by law; and for the purposes of responding to requests by government, a court of law or law enforcement authorities conducting an investigation.
The Episcopal Church uses your information where it is necessary to fulfill our legitimate interests, which include operating our websites, providing information and services described on our website, communicating with you via newsletters to which you subscribe, fulfilling contracts made with you, responding to your comments or questions, and informing you of areas of interest or services available.
The Episcopal Church retains your personal information for as long as is necessary to provide the services to you and to comply with legal obligations.  If you no longer want the Episcopal Church to use your personal information, you can request that we erase your personal information by contacting info@episcopalchurch.org; however, the Episcopal Church will retain information as is necessary for our legitimate business interests.  If you have questions about our privacy practices, please contact webmaster@episcopalchurch.org.
Some functions on our website are managed by third parties, which have their own data privacy policies.  The Episcopal Church encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from EpiscopalChurch.org and its family of websites so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information.  The Episcopal Church is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Episcopal Church family of websites or the websites to which we provide a link.
Digital Millennium Copyright Act Notice
Please notify the Episcopal Church if you believe that any of your intellectual property rights have been infringed.  Pursuant to Section 512 of the Copyright Act (“DMCA”), the Episcopal Church designates the following individual as its agent for receipt of notifications of claimed infringement: The Episcopal Church, Romy Mancini, rmancini@episcopalchurch.org, 815 Second Avenue, New York, New York 10017.  To be effective, the notification should include: (i) a physical or electronic signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the right being infringed; (ii) identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at the site; (iii) identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity, and information sufficient to permit us to locate the material; (iv) information sufficient to allow us to contact the complaining party; (v) a statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that the use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright or intellectual property owner, agent, or the law; and (vi) a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and, under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the right being infringed.  If you fail to comply with all of these requirements, your DMCA notification may not be valid.
The Episcopal ChurchWhat We Believe
What We Do
Who We Are
About Us
The Way of LoveThe Way of Love
Getting Started
Video Series
Podcast
